{
    "subject": "resource/2002\u201303_FC_Basel_season",
    "predicate": "property/goals",
    "object": "Leandro",
    "human_readable": "Leandro scored goals for FC Basel during the 2002\u201303 season.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8689766526222229,
            "question": "During what season did Leandro play for FC Basel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8656893968582153,
            "question": "How many goals did Leandro score for FC Basel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8493033051490784,
            "question": "Are there any records of Leandro's goals for FC Basel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8470349311828613,
            "question": "Is there any information about Leandro's performance statistics during the 2002\u201303 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7898476123809814,
            "question": "For which football club did Leandro score goals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.765287458896637,
            "question": "Was Leandro a successful player for FC Basel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089202404022217,
            "question": "What was Leandro's role in the FC Basel team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4573746621608734,
            "question": "Did Leandro play for any other clubs besides FC Basel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.320706844329834,
            "question": "What other achievements did Leandro have in his football career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26474690437316895,
            "question": "What position did Leandro play on the field?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leandro scored goals for FC Basel during the 2002\u201303 season.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1689_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other achievements did Leandro have in his football career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1689_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Leandro play for any other clubs besides FC Basel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1689_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Leandro's role in the FC Basel team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1689_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1689_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention Leandro Greco, but do not provide any information about him scoring goals for FC Basel during the 2002-03 season. In fact, there is no mention of Leandro scoring goals at all in the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Leandro scoring goals for FC Basel during the 2002-03 season. There is mention of a player named Leandro Tatu in one document, but no specific information regarding his goal-scoring activities or the 2002-03 season for FC Basel."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context indicating that Leandro played for FC Basel during the 2002\u201303 season.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states Leandro scored for FC Basel during the 2002\u201303 season, but context information mentions Basel qualifying for the knockout stages for the first time since the 2002-03 season. This implies Leandro played *after* that season.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no information about Leandro playing for FC Basel during the 2002\u201303 season, and previous context information does not support this statement.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Leandro scoring goals during the 2002\u201303 season. Moreover, the latest matchday and team-related details provided are from the 2013\u201314 season, which is several years after the 2002\u201303 season. Therefore, it can be reasonably concluded that any goal-scoring activities by Leandro for FC Basel would have been in more recent seasons.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}